A Guide to the Directors' Correspondence of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1933-1977 (bulk 1934-1976)
Library of Virginia
- Film Production Unit: Bohmer, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Film Production Unit: Bohmer, 1953 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Finance Committee: General, 1948-1950, folder 1 of 2 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Finance Committee: General, 1948-1950, folder 2 of 2 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Finance Committee: General, 1950 June - 1952 May, folder 1 of 2 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Finance Committee: General, 1950 June - 1952 May, folder 2 of 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Finance Committee: General, 1952-1954 [1] (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Finance Committee: General, 1952-1954 [2] (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Finance Committee: General, 1954 June - 1955 May (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Finance Committee: General, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Finance Committee: General, 1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 47)
- Finance Committee: General, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Finance Committee: Investment Reports, etc., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Finance Committee: Pending, 1939-1949 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Finances, 1969-1972 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Finances, 1969-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 48)
- Fire Regulations: Theatre re: Smoking, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- First and Merchants Trusts, 1969-1972 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- First and Merchants Trusts, 1969-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 49)
- Fitzroy, Herbert W.K., 1947-1953 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Fitzroy Memorial, 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Fitzroy Memorial, 1967-1968 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 50)
- Flags: Display, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Flint College and Cultural Development, 1957-1959 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Florence Agreement, National Committee for, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Flournoy, Horace S., 1953 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Flowers and Plants: Schedule and Purchases, 1954-1957 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Fogg Art Museum, 1935-1943 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Fogg Art Museum, 1935-1943 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 51)
- Fogg Art Museum, 1952-1960 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Fogg Art Museum, 1969-1974 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Folktale Puppets, 1953-1954 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Ford, Mrs. Henry, II, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Ford Exhibition: Virginia by Virginians, 1956 Feb 24 - Mar 11, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Ford Foundation, 1948-1952 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Ford Foundation, 1950-1959 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Ford Foundation: Correspondence, 1959-1970 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Ford Foundation: Jury Meeting 1958 Nov 24, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Ford Times, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Foreign Museum Directors Visit 1965 May 8, 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Foreign Newspapermen Luncheon, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Foreign Travel, 1972-1974 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- Form Letters, 1934-1940 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Forms from Israel, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Forms from Israel, 1959 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Forms: Giver's Lists and Letters, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 36)
- Fort Worth Art Museum, 1952-1958 (Box 34, Folder 37)
- Foundations, 1953-1961 (Box 34, Folder 38)
- Four Arts Magazine, 1934-1935 (Box 34, Folder 39)
- Fowler, Keith, 1969-1971 (Box 34, Folder 40)
- Francis, William, 1964-1968 (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Freeman, Douglas S., 1935-1939 (Box 34, Folder 42)
- Freeman, Douglas S., 1948-1963 (Box 34, Folder 43)
- French and Company, 1946-1959 (Box 34, Folder 44)
- French and Company, 1946-1959 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 52)
- Frick Art Reference Library, 1945-1950 (Box 34, Folder 45)
- Friday Evening Programs, 1949-1950 (Box 34, Folder 46)
- Friddell, Guy R., 1949-1952 (Box 34, Folder 47)
- Friends of Pompeii, 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 48)
- Friends of the Theatre (VMFA), 1965 (Box 34, Folder 49)
- Future Film Exhibition, 1964-1966 (Box 34, Folder 50)
- Future Film Exhibition, 1964-1966 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Fundraising, 1953-1957 (Box 34, Folder 51)
- G: General, 1934-1938 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- G: General, 1953-1954 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- G: General, 1953-1971, folder 1 of 3 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- G: General, 1953-1971, folder 2 of 3 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- G: General, 1953-1971, folder 3 of 3 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- G: General, 1953-1971 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 53)
- G: General, 1974-1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Gaines, Bill, 1974-1976 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Gaines, Bill: Correspondence, 1970-1972, folder 1 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Gaines, Bill: Correspondence, 1970-1972, folder 2 of 2 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Gaines, Bill: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 54)
- Galleries: General, 1972-1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Galleries: General, 1972-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 55)
- Galleries and Museums: General, 1953-1972 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Galleries and Museums: General, 1953-1972 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 23)
- Gallery Opening: 1954 Collections, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Gallery Talks, 1945-1948 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Gallery Talks: Virginia Women's Clubs, 1948-1949 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Garbisch, Col. Edgar, 1949-1958 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Garbisch, Col. Edgar, 1949-1958 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 56)
- Garden Club Dinner 1970 May 20, 1968-1970 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Garden Clubs, Federation of, 1958-1962 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Garner, Mrs. T. Fleetwood, 1964-1975 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Geiffert, Alfred II: Museum Landscape, 1957-1959 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- General Assembly, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- General Assembly: Sample Letter - Museum Promotion, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Gibbes Art Gallery, Charleston SC, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Gibson, George D., 1950-1958 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Gibson, George D., 1952-1962 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Gibson, George D., 1955-1956 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Gifts, 1965-1972 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Gifts, 1965-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 57)
- Glasgow, Arthur D., 1954-1958 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Glascow, Arthur G., 1954-1958 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 58)
- Godwin, Mills E., 1965-1972 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Goheen, Robert, 1956-1957 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Goldberg, Mrs. Arthur J., 1961 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- Goldsby, Robert, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Goodwin Memorial Commission, 1950-1952 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Goodwin Memorial Commission, 1950-1952 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 24)
- Gottwald, Elisabeth Shelton Fund, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Governor's Conference (1957), 1956-1957 (Box 90, Folder 33)
- Governor's Management Study, 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Governor's Office, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Governor's Office, 1974-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 59)
- Goya: General Nicholas Guye, 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Goya: General Nicholas Guye, 1971-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 60)
- Goya: Unveiling, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Graham, John M., 2nd, 1950-1952 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Gray, Garland, 1951-1954 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Gray, Horace A., 1948-1960 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Gray, Horace A., 1948-1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 61)
- Gray, Horace A., 1951-1959 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Gray, Horace A., 1951-1959 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 62)
- Grigaut, Paul L., 1962-1963 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Grigaut, Paul L., 1962-1965 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Grigaut, Paul L., 1962-1965 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 63)
- Guarding the Museum, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Guest, Raymond R., 1948-1966 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Guest, Raymond R., 1948-1966 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 64)
- Guide to Virginia Architecture, 1966-1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Gummerus, H. Olof, 1959-1961 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Gutman, Willi, 1972 June 1 - July 9, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- H: General, 1933-1940 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- H: General, 1973-1976 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- H: General, 1973-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 65)
- Ha-Hh: General, 1951-1972, folder 1 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Ha-Hh: General, 1951-1972, folder 2 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Ha-Hh: General, 1951-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 66)
- Hagins, Clarence, 1960-1971 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Hahn, Stephen Gallery, 1969-1972 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Hahn, Stephen Gallery, 1969-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 67)
- Haller, Harry, 1958-1959 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Hamaker, J.I., 1934-1942 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Hamaker, Mrs. J.I., 1935-1943 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Hampton Institute, 1940-1945 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- Harrison, Albertis S., Jr., 1961-1966 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Harrisonburg, Va. Mural, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- Harvard: 25th Reunion, 1955-1956 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Hayden-Eglevsky Co., 1957-1958 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Hayes, John G. Memorial Fund, 1946-1957 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Hayes, Mrs. John G., Sr., 1949-1954 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Hazeltine, Fred, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Healy Catalog: Material, 1950-1951 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Hearst Foundation, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Heckscher, August, 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Henry Russell Hitchcock, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- HEW, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- HEW Traveling Theatre, 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Hi-Hy: General, 1955-1972 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Hi-Hy: General, 1955-1972 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 25)
- Higgins, William H., Jr., 1959-1966 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Higgins, William H., Jr., 1959-1966 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 68)
- Highway Engineers: Tour and Lunch, 1967-1968 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Hirshhorn Museum / Sculpture Garden, 1973-1975 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Historical Society [VA] Meeting, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Hodges, LeRoy, 1935-1942 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Hoffer, Philip, 1965-1967 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Hoffman, Theodore, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Hoffmann Gold Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Hoffmann Gold Correspondence, 1963-1965 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 69)
- Hofheimer, Henry Clay II, 1959-1963 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Hofheimer, Henry Clay II, 1964-1971 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Holidays, 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Hollins College, 1946-1955 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Holton, Governor Linwood, 1935-1941 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Honors and Awards Committee, 1935-1941 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Honors and Awards Committee, 1939-1957 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Honors and Awards Committee, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 34)
- Hood, Paul, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Hood, Paul, 1974-1975 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 70)
- Hood, Paul, 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Hood, Paul, 1975-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 71)
- Hosho No Dance, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- Houdon Bust, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Houdon Bust, 1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 72)
- Houdon Bust of Pres. James Monroe, 1947-1951 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Houdon Bust of President James Monroe, 1947-1951 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 73)
- Houghton, Arthur A., Jr., 1961-1969 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Houghton, Arthur A., Jr., 1961-1969 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 26)
- Houghton, Arthur A., Jr., 1961-1969 (SLIDES) (Box 89, Folder 6-7)
- Houghton Gallery Luncheon, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Houston Museum of Fine Arts, 1953-1964 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- Houston, Nora, 1937-1940 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- Houston, Nora, 1937-1940 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 74)
- Howell, Charles R., 1953-1954 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- Hudnut, Joseph, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- Huldt, Ake H., 1953 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Humelsine, Carlisle H., 1959-1963 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Humelsine, Carlisle H., 1964-1968 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- Humelsine, Carlisle H., 1969-1972 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- I: General, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- I: General, 1945-1972 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- I: General, 1971-1974 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Inaugeration of Auditorium, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Information Alcoves, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Innocenti and Webel, 1964-1966 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Inquiries: Miscellaneous, 1935-1956 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Inquiries: Miscellaneous, 1935-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 75)
- Installation Ideas, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Institute of Public Affairs, University of Virginia, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Insurance: Boiler Policies, 1935-1955, folder 1 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Insurance: Boiler Policies, 1935-1955, folder 2 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Insurance: Boiler Policies, 1935-1955 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 76)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Damage Claims, 1949-1950 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Damage Claims, 1949-1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 77)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Damages, 1950-1953 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Damages, 1950-1953 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 78)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Damages, 1953-1956 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Damages, 1953-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 77, Folder 79)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Inventory and Endorsements, 1947-1955 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Inventory and Endorsements, 1947-1955 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Previous Inventories, 1947-1951 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Previous Inventories, 1947-1951 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Valuations, Samuels, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Insurance: Fine Arts - Valuations, Samuels, 1949 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Interim Museums, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- International Council of Museums (ICON), 1959-1967 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- International Council of Museums (ICON), 1970-1972, folder 1 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- International Council of Museums (ICON), 1970-1972, folder 2 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- International Council of Museums (ICON), 1972-1975 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- International Exhibitions Foundation, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- International Exhibitions Foundation, 1973-1976 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- International Exhibitions Foundation, 1973-1976 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 27)
- International Photographic Exposition, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Introduction for Catalog for: John Koch Exhibition, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Inventory: Art Owned by Museum, 1941-1947 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Inventory: Art Owned by Museum, 1941-1947 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Iron Fronts Preservation, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Iron Fronts Preservation, 1971 (OVERSIZE) (Box 84, Folder 28)
- J: General, 1934-1937 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- J: General, 1955-1970 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- J: General, 1955-1970 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 5)
- J: General, 1955-1972 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- J: General, 1955-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 6)
- J: General, 1973-1976 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Jackson, Howell E., 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Jamestown Celebration, 1953-1955 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Jamestown Celebration, 1953-1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Jamestown Celebration, 1955-1957 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Jamestown Celebration, 1955-1957 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Jamestown Celebration, 1955-1957 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Jamestown Exhibition, 1953-1957 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Jamestown Festival, 1952-1959 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Japanese Architecture, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Jazz Concert, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Jefferson Public Service Award, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Jenkins, Alfred Peyton, 1954-1957 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Johns, Jay W., 1935-1944 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Johns, Jay W., 1935-1944 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Johns, Jay W., 1950-1964 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Johnson, Ben, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Jones, T. Catesby, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Jones, Mrs. T. Catesby, 1950-1963 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Jones, Mrs. W. Ashby III, 1964-1970 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Jones, T. Catesby, 1941 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Joyner, Sarah, 1935-1945 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Judge the Jury, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Junior League Luncheon, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Junior League of Richmond, 1945-1952 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Junior League of Richmond, 1950-1954 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Junior Leagues of America Regional Conference, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- K: General, 1933-1939 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- K: General, 1946-1954 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- K: General, 1955-1972, folder 1 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- K: General, 1955-1972, folder 2 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- K: General, 1955-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 10)
- K: General, 1973-1976 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- K: General, 1973-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Karolik, Maxim, 1950-1964 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Karolik Collection, 1954-1955 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Katzenbach Lighting, 1964-1966 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1955-1966 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1955-1966 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Keppel, Dean Francis, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Keystone Jewelers Research Group, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- King, Martin Luther, Jr. Memorial Center, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Knoedler, M. and Co., 1946-1956 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Knoedler, M. and Co., 1946-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Knoll Associates, 1948-1964 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Koch, John, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Koenig, John, 1954-1958 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Koenig, John, 1954-1958 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Koenig, John, 1955-1963 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Koenig, John, 1958-1963 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Koenig, Mr.: Guest Promotion Director, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Koenig Memorial Collection, 1962-1965 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Kress Foundation, 1951-1961 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Kuhn, Mrs. Mary, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Kurtz, Le Roy, 1962-1964 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- L: General, 1952-1954 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- L: General, 1952-1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 13)
- L: General, 1955-1963 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- L: General, 1955-1963 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 14)
- L: General, 1956-1972, folder 1 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- L: General, 1956-1972, folder 2 of 2 (Box 39, Folder 45)
- L: General, 1956-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 15)
- L: General, 1971-1976 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Lady Lever Art Gallery, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- LaTrobe Theatre, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- Lecture: Opinion in the Provinces, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Lecture: U. of Minnesota, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Lecture: Urban Conference, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Lecture Programs 1947-1948, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Lecture Programs 1948-1949, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Lecture Programs: Wednesday evenings, 1946-1947 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Lectures 1952-1953, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Lectures, etc. by Leslie Cheek, Jr., 1958-1965 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Lecturers: Information, 1949-1952 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Leisure, Major, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Leisure, Major, 1970-1971 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Let's Go, 1961-1966 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Lewis, Mr. and Mrs. Sydney, 1967-1972 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Lewis, Mr. and Mrs. Sydney, 1967-1972 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Lexington VA (Historic Foundation, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Liebes, Dorothy, 1963-1968 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Lighting: Other Museums, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Lighting Reprints (Electrical Construction and Maintenance, February 1959), 1960 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Linton Collection of African Sculpture, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Lists (Old): Art Organizations, Schools, etc., 1934-1937 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Loan of Furnishings, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Loans from Collections, 1947-1949 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Loans from Collections, 1947-1949 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Loans from Permanent Collection, 1950-1951 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Loans from Permanent Collections, 1950-1951 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Loans from Permanent Collection, 1952-1953 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Loans to Embassies, 1961-1964 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Long Beach Museum of Art, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Los Angeles County Museum, 1970-1973 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Louvre, Palais du, 1959-1963 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Lusk, Carroll B., 1953-1958 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Lusk, Carroll B., 1953-1958 (RESTRICTED OVERSIZE) (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Lusklite, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Lynchburg Fine Arts Center, 1961-1965 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Lynes, Russell, 1954-1960 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- M: General, 1934-1940 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- M: General, 1971-1976 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- M: General, 1971-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 20)
- M: General, 1972-1976 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- M: General, 1972-1976 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Ma-Mc: General, 1958-1972 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Macbeth Galleries, 1935-1945 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Macbeth Galleries, 1935-1945 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 22)
- Magazines and Bulletins: Back Issues, Orders and Correspondence, 1946-1949, folder 1 of 2 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Magazines and Bulletins: Back Issues, Orders and Correspondence, 1946-1949, folder 2 of 2 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Magnasco Painting, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Magnasco Painting, 1954 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 23)
- Mailing Lists: Catalogues, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Mailing Schedules, 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 41)
- Maillol: "La Riviere" Acquisition, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 42)
- Maillol: "La Riviere" Acquisition, 1970-1971 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 24)
- Maillol: "La Riviere" Acquisition, 1970-1971 (SLIDES) (Box 89, Folder 8-9)
- Manship, Paul, 1936-1938 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- Mariners Museum, 1970-1974 (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Marsh, Robert T., Jr., 1952-1967 (Box 40, Folder 45)
- Marshall, George C., Research Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 46)
- Marshall, John (Portrait), 1955-1956 (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Marshall, John (Portrait), 1955-1956 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 25)
- Martin, Gerry J., 1965-1969 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Martin, Gerry J., 1965-1969 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 26)
- Mary Baldwin College, 1956-1964 (Box 40, Folder 49)
- Mary Washington College, 1949-1964 (Box 40, Folder 50)
- Mason, Frank E., 1962 (Box 40, Folder 51)
- Massie, Mrs. William R., 1936-1937 (Box 40, Folder 52)
- Master Drawings from Cooper Union, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 53)
- Masterpieces of American Silver, 1959-1960 (Box 40, Folder 54)
- Masterpieces of Chinese Art, 1954-1955 (Box 40, Folder 55)
- Masterpieces of Chinese Art, 1954-1955 (OVERSIZE) (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Material (samples, etc.), 1937-1939 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Matson, Lowell, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Mattern, J.J., Jr. (Virginia Artists), 1935 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- McCarthy, Frank, 1957-1966 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- McClellan, Edward T., 1955-1958 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- McCormack, Helen, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- McCormick, Thomas Julian Jr., 1953-1969 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- McFee, Henry Lee (Virginia Artists), 1937-1938 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Me-My: General, 1958-1970, folder 1 of 2 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Me-My: General, 1958-1970, folder 2 of 2 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Me-My: General, 1969-1971 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Me-My, 1969 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 27)
- Medieval Hall Opening, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Mediterranean Culture, Institute of - University of Richmond, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Meeks, Carroll L.V., 1950-1953 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Melchers, Mrs. Gari, 1935-1955 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Melchers, Mrs. Gari, 1935-1955 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 28)
- Melchers, Mrs. Gari, 1946-1956 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Melchers Estate, 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Melchers Memorial Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Melchers Memorial Committee, 1956-1957 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 29)
- Melchers Memorial Committee, 1956-1961 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Melchers Memorial Committee, 1956-1961 (RESTRICTED OVERSIZE) (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Mellon (A.W.) Educational and Charitable Trust, 1953-1957 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Mellon, Paul, 1938-1962 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Mellon, Paul, 1938-1962 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 30)
- Mellon, Paul, 1950-1969 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Mellon, Paul, 1950-1969 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 31)
- Mellon, Paul, 1962-1964 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Mellon, Paul, 1962-1964 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 32)
- Members' Lecture Series: Spring, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Members' Letter: September 1972, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Members' Loan Library, 1949-1950 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Members' Loan Library, 1949-1950 (RESTRICTED) (Box 78, Folder 33)
- Membership, 1970-1975 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Membership Campaign 1954, 1954-1955 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Membership Campaign 1956-1957, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Membership Campaign 1957-1958, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 30)